A Finding Aid to the Donald Saff papers and Saff Tech Arts Records, circa 1710, 1800-2013 bulk 1965-2010, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Saff Tech Arts Records, circa 1970-2013; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 22.2 Linear feet Boxes 10-32, 34; .640 Gigabytes ER010-ER011
  - Artist Files, circa 1970-2010; 2.2; Archival Resource Key; 15.2 Linear feet Boxes 12-27, 33; 0.64 Gigabytes ER010-ER011
    - Roy Lichtenstein, Archival Resource Key
      - Correspondence, Outgoing Inquiry, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, Sales (General), circa 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, Crating and Shipping, circa 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, Galerie Thaddeus Ropac, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, Janus Avison Gallery, circa 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 25-27)
      - Correspondence, Shelley Lee (Copyright Agent), 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, Gagosian Gallery, circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, Microcraft Inc. (Fabrication), circa 1993-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, Metal Master (Framing), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, Joe Sacco (Shipping), circa 1991, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, Jack B. Scherr (Fine Art Ltd.), circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, Swiss Foundry (Fabrication), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, Neil Weisman, 1993, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, circa 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Exhibition, Print Retrospective at NGA (Oct. 1994-Jan. 1995), Press, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - Exhibition, Art for the World (Fall 1997, Spring 1998), circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - Exhibition, Bank of New York, Carriage House Viewing (with Rauschenberg) (Mar. 11 1998), circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 40)
      - Exhibition, Retrospective at Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes, Mexico City (Jun.-Sep. 1999), circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 41)
      - Inventory (STA), circa 1990-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
      - Inventory, circa 2000-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Invoices, circa 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Invoices, John Berggruen Gallery, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Invoices, John F. Cooke Walt Disney Co., circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Invoices, Knoedler & Co., 1994, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Quotations, Sales, circa 1998-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Sales, Drawings and Collages Prices, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Reflections On Expressionist Painting (1990), Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 10)
        - Documentation, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence, Knoedler & Co., circa 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 12)
        - Invoices, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 13)
        - Packing Instructions, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 14)
        - Notes, Carnegie Hall, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Suspended Mobile (1990), Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 16)
        - Documentation, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 17)
        - Correspondence, Howard Barnett, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 18)
        - Correspondence, Knoedler & Co., circa 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 19)
        - Exhibition, Knoedler & Co. (Oct.-Nov. 1991), circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 20)
        - Invoices, circa 1990, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 21)
        - Handling Instructions, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 22)
        - Notes, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 23)
        - Magna Color Samples, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Waterlilies (1992), Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 25)
        - Correspondence (General), circa; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 26-27)
        - Correspondence, Acquavella Galleries, circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 28)
        - Correspondence, Joseph Horn, circa; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 29)
        - Correspondence, Irving Galleries Palm Beach, circa 1992-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 30)
        - Correspondence, Jim Goodman Gallery, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 31)
        - Correspondence, Knoedler & Co., circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 32)
        - Correspondence, Leslie Freely Fine Art, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 33)
        - Correspondence, Marjories Margolis Gallery, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 34)
        - Catalog, Karen Ellis, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 35)
        - Catalog, Essay by Frederic Tuten, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 36)
        - Documentation, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 37-38)
        - Documentation, Waterlilies with Japanese Bridge, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 39)
        - Documentation, Waterlilies, Blue Lily Pads, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 40)
        - Documentation, Waterlilies, Pink Flower, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 41)
        - Documentation, Waterlilies with Willow, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 42)
        - Documentation, Waterlilies, Pond with Reflections, 1993, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 43)
        - Documentation, Waterlily with Cloud, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 44)
        - Exhibition, Richard Gray Gallery (Oct. 1992), Archival Resource Key
          - Correspondence, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence, Inbound, circa 1992, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 2)
          - Shipping, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 3)
          - Consignment, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 4)
          - Catalog, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 5)
          - Invoices, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 6)
          - Damages, circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 7)
        - Exhibition, Leo Castelli Gallery (Nov.-Dec. 1992), Archival Resource Key
          - General, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 8)
          - Correspondence, circa 1992-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 9)
          - Catalog, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 10)
          - Sales, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 11)
          - Shipping, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 12)
          - Invoices, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 13)
        - Exhibition, Mayor Gallery (Nov.-Dec. 1992), Archival Resource Key
          - General, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 15)
          - Invoices, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 16)
          - Shipping, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 17)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Kaj Forsblom (Dec. 1992), Archival Resource Key
          - Correspondence, In, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 18)
          - Correspondence, Out, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 19)
          - Catalog, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 20)
          - Consignments, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 21)
          - Shipping, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 22)
          - Invoices, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 23)
          - Damage and Restoration, circa 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 24)
          - Insurance Claim (Damage), circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 25)
        - Exhibition, Bobbie Greenfield Fine Art (Jan.-Feb. 1993), circa 1993-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 26)
        - Exhibition, Akira Ikeda Gallery (Feb. 1993), Archival Resource Key
          - General, circa 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 27)
          - Correspondence, circa 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 28)
          - Catalog, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 29)
          - Consignment & Invoice, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 30)
          - Sale, Waterlilies with Cloud, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 31)
          - Sale, Waterlilies, Pink Flower, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 32)
          - Press, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 33)
          - Shipping, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 34)
        - Exhibition, Greenberg van Doren Gallery (Apr.-May 1993), Archival Resource Key
          - General, circa 1993, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 35)
          - Correspondence, Incoming, circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 36)
          - Consignment, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 37)
          - Damage, circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 38)
          - Sale, Waterlilies with Japanese Bridge, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 39)
        - Exhibition, Barbara Mathes Gallery (May 1993), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 40)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Lehman (Sep. 1993), Archival Resource Key
          - Correspondence, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 41)
          - Correspondence, Incoming, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 42)
          - Catalog, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 43)
          - Consignment, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 44)
          - Invoices, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 45)
          - Shipping, circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 46)
        - Exhibition, Susan Sheehan Gallery (Sep. 1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 47)
        - Exhibition, Ron Hall Gallery (Nov. 1993), Archival Resource Key
          - Correspondence, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 48)
          - Invoices, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 49)
          - Damage, circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 50)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Thaddaeus Ropac (Unrealized), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 51)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Daniel Templon (Unrealized), circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 52)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Hans Strelow (Unrealized), 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 53)
        - Loans, Waterlily with Reflections Tel Aviv Museum (July-Nov. 2004), circa 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 54)
        - Expenses, circa 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
        - Expenses, Art Supplies, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
        - Cost Estimates (Swirl), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Invoices, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 8)
        - Invoices (Knoedler & Co.), circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 9)
        - Invoices, circa 1992-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 10-11)
        - Invoices, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12)
        - Invoices Spencer Genger, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 13)
        - Inventory (RL92-006 - RL92-008), circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 14)
        - Inventory, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 15)
        - Inventory (June 1999), circa 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 16)
        - Accounting, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 17)
        - Personnel Costs, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 18)
        - Signatures, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 19)
        - Metal Frame List, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 20)
        - Shipping, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 21)
        - Handling Instructions, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 22)
        - Shipping, Steve Belkin, circa 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 23)
        - Press, Ads, Art in America Nov. 1992, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Metallic Brushstroke Head (1994), Archival Resource Key
        - Documentation, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 25)
        - Correspondence, Walla Walla Foundry, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 26)
        - Correspondence, Sales, circa 1993-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 27)
        - Correspondence, Sales, Knoedler & Co., circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 28)
        - Consignment, Leo Castelli Gallery, circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 29)
        - Consignment, Pace Wildenstein Gallery, circa 1999, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 30)
        - Brushtronic Engineering, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 31)
        - Production, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 32)
        - Fabrication, circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Woman Contemplating a Yellow Cup (1995), Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
        - Documentation, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2)
        - Research and Development, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, A. Boser, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, Bennet, Grutman, and Gideon Strauss, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence, Sash Spencer, circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, Trans Resources Inc., circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence, Greenberg van Doren Gallery, circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 8)
        - Consignment, James Goodman Gallery, circa 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - Repair (Keith Barish), circa 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 10)
        - Photographs, Color Copies, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Imperfect (1995) Documentation, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Brushstroke Still-Life (1997), Archival Resource Key
        - Documentation, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 13)
        - Exhibition, Odakyu Museum, Tokyo (Mar.-Apr. 1998), circa 1997-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 14)
        - Consignment, Greenberg van Doren Gallery, circa 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 15)
        - Production, circa 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 16)
        - Catalog Images, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 17)
        - Printing, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 18)
        - Color Draw Downs, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 19)
        - Framing, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 20)
        - Crating (Arnold Factory Supply), circa 1993-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 21)
        - Uncrating Instructions, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Woman Contemplating a Yellow Cup, Imperfect, Notes, circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Suspended Mobile, Waterlilies Distribution Agreements (Knoedler & Co.), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Mural Drawing Plans for Chapel of the Eucharist Commission (Unrealized) (Apr.1997), circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Waterlilies, Suspended Mobile Oval Frame, Project Notes, circa 1992-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Wall Explosion II, Repair (Sonnabend Gallery, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - Sculpture Notes, circa 1992-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Editions, Artist Proof Information, circa 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Writings, "Contemporary Prints from the Lilja Collection", circa 1995-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Publication, Roy Lichtenstein's Last Still-Life) Cornell University, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 31-32)
      - Publication, Roy Lichtenstein's Last Still-Life, Galleria Lawrence Rubin (1998), circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 33-34)
      - Publication, Still-Life Catalog, Tuten Essay (Watkins, Loomis Agency), circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 35)
      - Royalties, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - Signatures, circa 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - Signatures, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - RL Visits, circa 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 38)
      - Press Clippings, circa 1992-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 39-40)
      - Printed Material, Miscellaneous, circa 1986, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 41)
      - Research Material, Micro Craft and Viewpoint, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 42)
      - Wax and Ink Formulas, circa 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Packing and Crating, circa 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Robert Mapplethorpe, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Brice Marden, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Irina Nakhova, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Martin Puryear, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Robert Rauschenberg, Archival Resource Key
      - Correspondence, Archival Resource Key
        - Akira Ikeda Gallery, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 7)
        - Anthony d'Offay Gallery, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 8)
        - Art in America, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 9)
        - Art in America Dispute, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 10)
        - Morton Beebe, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 11)
        - Bernard Jacobson Gallery, circa 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 12)
        - Thomas Buehler, circa 1991-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 13)
        - Felissimo, circa 1994-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 14)
        - Galerie Beyeler, circa 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
        - Galerie Jamileh Weber, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 17)
        - Galleria Lawrence Rubin, circa 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
        - Joshua J. Kaufman (Copyright Lawyer), circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 20)
        - Theodore Kheel, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 21)
        - John B. Koegel Esq., circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 22)
        - Irena Hochman Fine Art Ltd., circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 23)
        - Gagosian Gallery, circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 24)
        - Graphicstudio, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 25)
        - Guggenheim Foundation, circa 1999-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 26)
        - Hiroko Ikegami, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 27)
        - Alfred Kren, Conflict and Settlement, circa 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 28-29)
        - Le Marie Tranier Gallery, circa 1991-19931; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 30)
        - Anne Livet, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 31)
        - Leslie Mazza, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 32)
        - Mixographia (Luis Remba), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 33)
        - Musee des Beaux Arts Montreal, circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 34)
        - National Gallery of Art, circa 1988-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 35)
        - Pace McGill, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - Pace Prints, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - Pace Wildenstein, circa 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Pace Wildenstein (Arne Glimcher), circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 4)
        - Darryl Pottorf, circa 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 5)
        - Robert Rauschenberg, circa 1989-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 6-9)
        - Robert Rauschenberg Foundation, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - Carol Rosenberg, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 11)
        - Sonnabend Gallery, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 12)
        - Texas Gallery, Fredericka Hunter, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 13)
        - Untitled Press, General, circa 1998-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
        - Untitled Press, Contract Agreement, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 16)
        - Untitled Press, Bradley Jeffries, circa 1991-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 17-21)
        - Ubu Gallery (Rosa Esman), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 22)
        - Venable LLP (Copyright), 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 23)
        - Visual Artists and Galleries Association (VAGA), circa 1997-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 24-25)
        - Wetterling Gallery, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 26-27)
        - David White, circa 1991-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 28-35)
        - Terry van Blunt Conflict, circa 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 36)
        - Reproduction Permissions, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 37-38)
        - Gifts to Brooklyn Museum, circa 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 39)
      - Exhibition, Seven Master Printmakers: Innovations of the 1980s, MoMA, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Exhibition, Galerie Jamileh Weber (May 1993), circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Exhibition, Knoedler & Co. (May-June 1993), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Exhibition,Taejŏn Expo '93 (Aug.-Nov. 1993), Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, Amway Corp., circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence, Nancy L. Pressly, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 6)